Hello everyone, welcome to another video.
This time it's something new here on my channel.
about sportswear but make it cool so not frilly flowery whatever girly sportswear
with cool stuff which I'm going to show you so stay tuned already wearing the
first outfit for our change it's a combination with the shorts which is
pretty unusual for me I don't think I own any sports shorts whatever but I
I like the length and some top with an under boob cleavage and as I said I'm not really
the most sportive person or your average fitness influencer so I wanted to I don't know show
you something that is rather cool and I think this set is great together I like it pretty
much and I'm going to show you some different colors and lengths later in the
video but for now it's this. The outfits are from a brand called Firm Abs and
thanks for the support for this video. Of course I'll link everything down below
in the description box. If you have any questions leave a comment and yeah check
everything out down there. This is the outfit you've already seen in the intro
video. It's a jacket and some leggings and the leggings have this cargo style again with the
pockets here at the booty and I really like that the arms of the jacket are really long
and that there's a zipper which is slightly shiny. So yeah love this combination it works
great together. I was looking for sportswear that is more alternative and
which I could actually wear also in my daily life. I'm pretty sure I'm going to
wear this jacket someday at the office for example and that I'm going to wear
this pants for, I don't know, buying groceries or stuff because it's just not
just sportswear but it looks really cool. Okay and with this approach that I want
wear this also on a daily basis I'm going to try something. I'm going to change my shoes and see
how these cool leggings look with some heels. Okay I have to say I like it.
It looks cool now the leggings are long enough with the higher shoes and I unzipped the jacket
a bit so it's a completely different look somehow and I like it what do you prefer the
Nike sneakers or some heels I think the leggings can go with both for sure
so after two black outfits I'm going to bring in some color and change into something different
than black. Okay from high heels to no heels. To be honest normally I don't wear shoes when I'm
doing sports. So yeah this is a bit similar to the first outfit from the cut of the top although
there is a zipper here which you can really open and close. It's just a nice design feature and it
it's a rather firm grip here and the pants are again a bit cargo style-ish but totally different
color and the cut here is different and I like the triangular shape here a lot. I really wanted
to show you at least one color in this video and although I don't like kind of bright blue and white
and orange I settled for this one and I have to say I quite like it. It somehow works together
with my hair and my skin tone. So that's cool and I've already worn this once before when
Fux Teufelswild visited me and we took some pictures and we also did a double furmaps
photo shoot set. And now it's time for the last outfit and it's going to be black again.
And tada! Last outfit, some mesh combination and I have to say I love mesh and now it is combined with sportswear which is pretty cool.
Actually I already wore this outfit for a workout session so I can tell you it's pretty comfortable.
It worked out great and I'm not used to having long arms for workouts so I was
kind of confused that all the sweat is absorbed by the top but on the other
hand it can't run down your arms which is kind of good. Alright but I love the
top I love that it's asymmetrical with the mesh part and the leggings are on a
a plain with a mesh at the front. I think this is kind of one of my favorite
outfits. I like all of them, I can't decide which one is my favorite so far.
Pretty sure that the jacket is place one because it's so cool and I'm going to
wear it on lots of occasions. Anyway I hope you had fun with this video. I hope
I could show you some cool spots where stuff and I wish you a nice evening or
day or whatever see you around bye